Wait, what?
He is the Knights'
head coach?
Of course!
If it wasn't
for Coach Ted
joining our
team this year,
we never would
have made the finals.
Coach Ted,
I am a die-hard
Knights fan.
Coach Ted,
you're kind of a
personal hero of mine.
Would...
Would you mind
taking a picture
with me?
Yeah, of course.
Oh my gosh,
this is the best.
I can't believe this.
I just met the head
coach of the Knights.
I'm going to
be telling
everybody about this.
Thank you so much.
Of course.
Dad.
This is what I came home to celebrate with you.
I...
I'm taking my team
to the Super Bowl.
Son...
Is it really true?
No way!
That guy is
obviously an actor
you paid to
trick us!
There's no way
you're the head coach
of a championship-
contending team.
Come on.
Just admit it.
You are a nobody,
a fraud.
You'll end up
just like your
broke old father,
scraping by for life.
You can insult me
all you want,
but don't you dare
insult my father.
Enough!
So what if you
made the stupid finals?
Today is your
grandfather's birthday.
Did you bring
him any gifts?